webvision2020.com 2011-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Web Vision 2020

##### Privacy Policy

The community known as the Web Vision 2020 **_(Community)_** is operated by   (ABN  ) **_(we, us,_** or **_our)_**. This Privacy Policy relates to the collection, disclosure, use and storage of personal information handled by us in relation to the Community. We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your personal information in accordance with Australian privacy laws.

###### Why we collect personal information

We mainly collect personal information to enable you to be involved in the Community. Generally, if you choose not to provide personal information, you may not be able to be involved in the Community.

###### The type of personal information we collect

We collect and store certain personal information. The type of information we collect largely depends on whether you use the website at <http://www.webvision2020.com/> **_(Website)_** and are a user **_(User)_** or are a member of the Community **_(Member)_** or have become a contact of ours through other means **_(Contact)._**

If you are a Member, the nature of personal information collected by us may include your name, postal address, postcode, capital city, state, country, telephone number, work number, mobile number, occupation, company name, company address, email address, bank account, credit card details, favourite book, aspirations for the future, star sign, URL, personal opinions and reviews of publications, personal information in any messages, posts or attachments sent through the Community, and other associated personal information.

If you are a User or Contact, the nature of personal information collected by us may include your name, postal address, postcode, state, country, telephone number, mobile number, occupation, company name, email address, URL, personal information in any messages, posts or attachments sent through the Community, and other associated personal information.

If you are a Member or User, some of the information we collect and store may also be sensitive information about you, but we only collect and store sensitive information that you have chosen to provide us through the Community.

If you are a User or Member of the Website, we also collect certain cookies and other session variables relating to your use of the Website. Such information may include:

  * Your server address
  * The type of browser you use
  * Your date and time of access
  * Your time usage of the Website
  * The amount of time you log in per month
  * The pages accessed and documents downloaded
  * The number of items you downloaded
  * The previous sites you visited
  * The number of pages you viewed

If you visit the Website using one of our affiliates’ links, we use a cookie to keep track of your visit, so we can correctly pay the affiliate a commission if you make a purchase. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or it may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting the Website.

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies.

However, if you do so, you may be unable to access certain sections of the Website or you may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customise the Website’s features according to your preferences.

###### Collection of Personal Information

How we collect and store personal information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you choose to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you make a purchase, when you participate in the interactive areas of our site (such as message boards or chat rooms), when you register for access to certain sections of our websites or when you request certain features such as newsletters, special reports, or e-books.

We do not collect any personal information unless the information is necessary to enable us to perform one or more of our functions and activities. We only identify you personally if you give us this information voluntarily. We will take all reasonable precautions to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when it is no longer required for our functions and activities.

If you are a Member, we may collect personal information if you:

  * Register to become a Member 
  * Contact us through the Website 
  * Create or update your Member profile on the Website
  * Send email correspondence through the Website to other Members
  * Participate in the online forum 
  * Request support or statistics through the Website
  * Comment on products listed on the Website 
  * Purchase a product or service listed on the Website
  * Use the live chat feature on the Website
  * Post letters, send facsimile transmissions, or email correspondence to us or contact us by telephone
  * Supply us with your business cards
  * Provide your personal information to us in other similar instances

If you are a User, we may collect personal information if you:

  * Contact us through the Website
  * Use the live chat feature on the Website
  * Purchase a product or service listed on the Website
  * Visit the Website using one of our affiliate links
  * Post letters, send facsimile transmissions, or email correspondence to us or contact us by telephone
  * Provide your personal information to us in other similar instances

If you are a Contact, we may collect personal information if you:

  * Have contact with us
  * Are referred by a friend
  * Supply us with your business cards
  * Post letters, send facsimile transmissions, or email correspondence to us or contact us by telephone
  * Provide your personal information to us in other similar instances

We will generally collect personal information from you directly however we may from time to time collect personal information about you from your friends, Users, Members or other third parties such as private label partners, the licensor of the underlying system for operating the Community, credit reporting agencies or publicly available sources of information.

###### Use Personal Information

If you are a Member, we may use your personal information to:

  * Manage your membership 
  * Arrange payment of your membership fees and other fees
  * Send newsletters to you
  * Provide or advertise a product or service to you
  * Assist with the purchase and delivery of products
  * Facilitate communication between you and other Members of the Community 
  * Facilitate communication between you and private label partners in the Community 
  * To notify you of seminars, events, special offers, products and services for sale
  * Send you a birthday message
  * Allow you to post and respond to posted information
  * Allow you to review content on the Website
  * Allow you to inform other Members of your opinion of listed books, items and audio
  * Allow you to view upcoming seminars
  * Offer promotions and advertisements
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests
  * Allow you to participate in the forum feature
  * Allow you to participate in the live chat feature
  * Provide IT support and other general assistance to Members
  * Direct market to you if that you have provided consent for such a purpose
  * Enhance and research our services 
  * Improve our Website content

If you are a User, we may use your personal information to:

  * Assist with the purchase and delivery of products
  * Direct market to you if you have provided consent for such a purpose
  * Send newsletters to you
  * Send introductory emails to you
  * Respond to your inquiries
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests
  * Enhance and research our services 
  * Improve our Website content
  * Allow you to participate in the live chat feature

If you are a Contact, we may use your personal information to:

  * Send introductory emails to you
  * Send newsletters to you
  * Direct market to you if you have provided consent for such a purpose

In addition to the above, we may also use personal information for any other related use if the related use would be within your reasonable expectations or for any other purpose to which you give your express or implied consent and as otherwise provided in Australian privacy laws.

From time to time we may also email you with news, information and offers relating to our own products and services or those of selected partners.

###### Disclosure of Personal Information

If you are a Member, in order to fulfil the purposes set out above, we may disclose your personal information to:

  * Other Members of the Website
  * The licensor of the underlying system for operating the Community
  * Mailing houses
  * Your representatives and credit reporting agencies
  * Our professional advisors
  * Government and regulatory authorities or other organisations as required by law
  * Organisations involved in the transfer or sale of all or part of our assets or business
  * Outsourced service providers who manage the services we provide to you including customer enquiries, mailing systems, billing and debt recovery functions, information technology services, marketing services and market research
  * Our related entities and businesses

If you are a User or Contact, in order to fulfil the purposes set out above, we may disclose your personal information to:

  * The licensor of the underlying system for operating the Community
  * Mailing houses
  * Your representatives and credit reporting agencies
  * Our professional advisors
  * Government and regulatory authorities or other organisations as required by law
  * Organisations involved in the transfer or sale of all or part of our assets or business
  * Outsourced service providers who manage the services we provide to you including customer enquiries, mailing systems, information technology services, marketing services and market research
  * Our related entities and businesses

For all purchases processed through the Website, we use a payment gateway called Secure Pay, which is one of the largest and most respected in Australia, to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card transactions over the Internet. Personal and confidential information including your credit card details are encrypted the moment they are transmitted from your browser to the banking network using industry standard SSL 128-bit encryption technology. The only company who has access to this data is ANZ Banking Corporation.

###### Direct Marketing

We may use your personal information (other than sensitive information) for the purpose of direct marketing. If you do not wish to receive direct marketing information, please let us know by contacting our Privacy Officer at the address listed below. We will then take steps to ensure that you do not receive any direct marketing information in the future.

###### Data Quality

We will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and/or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. To assist us in achieving this objective, please contact us if any of your details change or if you believe your details are not accurate, complete and up to date.

###### Data Security

Personal information collected by us is typically stored on servers and content management software operated by us or our licensors. We will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information against misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Access to your personal information is strictly limited to those staff who need to know such information in order to fulfil the purpose of collection.

###### Access and Correction

You have a right to access the personal information we hold about you by making your request in writing to us at the address listed below. We will provide such access subject to the exceptions under the Australian privacy laws.

We reserve the right to charge a fee for searching and providing access to your information.

If you are a User, Member or Contact of the Website, you can update your contact information at any time by clicking on the “Support” button and then “My Account” on the Website. We strongly suggest that you check this area regularly, in order to make sure that you continue to received our regular email updates and we can contact you by phone or mail for important announcements. You can also update your payment details in the area.

###### Anonymity

You are free to use the Website anonymously by not identifying yourself. You have the option of remaining anonymous in circumstances where you may be giving us feedback, by not providing any of your personal information.

###### Transborder data flows

We will only transfer your personal information overseas in order to perform one or more of our functions and activities. In such circumstances, we will either obtain your express or implied consent or use our reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is handled consistently with the Australian privacy laws.

###### Children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from or about children under 18 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any personal information from a child under 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us at the address listed below.

###### Links to other sites

Where this site contains links to other sites, we do not accept responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We encourage other suitable websites to include a link back to this site provided you DO NOT use any trademarks or copyright information without permission and that you do not link to this site from a site or in a manner which disparages the Website, us or our directors, employees, agents or suppliers.

If you would like to arrange a link, please contact us by email.

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you to take into account new laws and technology, changes to our operations and practices and the changing business environment.

###### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions in relation to privacy, please contact our Privacy Officer at:

Webvision 2020  
PO Box 410  
Bunbury WA, Australia, 6231  
Email: info@webvision2020.info  
Telephone (within Australia): (08) 9791 6600  
Telephone (outside Australia): +61 8 9791 6600
